Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Edit: 1973: Russia (Offsite-box 460, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1973: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1974: America (Offsite-box 460, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1974: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) [empty] (Offsite-box 460, Folder 29)
  - Edit: 1974: Organization (Offsite-box 460, Folder 30)
  - Edit: 1974: Russia (Offsite-box 460, Folder 31)
  - Edit: 1974: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460, Folder 32)
  - Edit: 1975: America (Offsite-box 460, Folder 33)
  - Edit: 1975-1976: Far East (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1975-1976: Far East [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1975: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 460, Folder 35)
  - Edit: 1975: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460, Folder 36)
  - Edit: 1975: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1976: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1976: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1976: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1977: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1977: Freedom of the Press (Offsite-box 461, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1977: Organization: Louis Banks survey: Attitudinal Survey of Editorial Employees (Offsite-box 461, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1977: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1977: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1978: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1978: Freedom of the Press (Offsite-box 461, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1978: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1978: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1979: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1979: Editor-In-Chief: Donvan/Grunwald Transition (Offsite-box 461, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1979: Mid East (Offsite-box 461, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1979: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1979: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1980: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1980-1981: American Renewal (Offsite-box 461, Folder 20-21)
  - Edit: 1981: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1981: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1981: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1982: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1982: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1982: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1983: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1983: Israel-Sharon (Offsite-box 461, Folder 29-31)
  - Edit: 1983: Israel-Sharon (2) (Offsite-box 461)
  - Edit: 1983: Israel-Sharon (2) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1983: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 34)
  - Edit: 1983: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 35)
  - Edit: 1984: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 36)
  - Edit: 1985: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 37)
  - Edit: 1986: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 38)
  - Edit: 1986: Freedom of the Press (Offsite-box 461, Folder 39)
  - Edit: 1986: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 40)
  - Edit: 1986: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 41)
  - Edit: 1987: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 42)
  - Edit: 1987: Editor-in-Chief: Grunwald/McManus Transition (Offsite-box 461, Folder 43)
  - Edit: 1987: Freedom of the Press (Offsite-box 461, Folder 44)
  - Edit: 1987: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 45)
  - Edit: 1988: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 47)
  - Edit: 1988: Freedom of the Press [empty] (Offsite-box 461, Folder 48)
  - Edit: 1988: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 49)
  - Edit: 1988: Miscellaneous [empty] (Offsite-box 461, Folder 50)
  - Edit: 1989: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 51)
  - Edit: 1989: Freedom of the Press [empty] (Offsite-box 461, Folder 52)
  - Edit: 1989: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 53)
  - Edit: 1989: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 54)
  - Edit: 1990: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 55)
  - Edit: 1990: Freedom of the Press [empty] (Offsite-box 461, Folder 56)
  - Edit: 1990: Organization (Offsite-box 461, Folder 57)
  - Edit: 1990: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 461, Folder 58)
  - Edit: 1991: America (Offsite-box 461, Folder 59)
  - Edit: 1991: Freedom of the Press (Offsite-box 462, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1991: Middle East: Persian Gulf (Offsite-box 462, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1991: Organization (Offsite-box 462, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1991: Russia (Offsite-box 462, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1991: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1992: America (Offsite-box 462, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1992: Freedom of the Press [empty] (Offsite-box 462, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1992: Organization (Offsite-box 462, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1992: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1993: Organization (Offsite-box 462, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1993: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1994: Editor-in-Chief: McManus/Pearlstine Transition (Offsite-box 462, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1994: Organization (Offsite-box 462, Folder 12.1)
  - Edit: 1994: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1995: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1995: Organization (Offsite-box 462, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1997: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 462, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 2012: Time Inc. Editorial Guidelines (Offsite-box 462, Folder 17)
  - Editorial Services: 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 462, Folder 18-19)
  - Editorial Services: 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 462)
  - Editorial Services: 1967-1970 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Editorial Services: 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 462, Folder 22-23)
  - Editorial Services: 1975: Iranian Proposal (Offsite-box 462, Folder 24)
  - Editorial Services: 1976 & Later (Offsite-box 462)
  - Editorial Services: 1976 & Later [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Editorial Technology (Offsite-box 462, Folder 27)
  - Editorial Services: Presentation (Offsite-box 462, Folder 28-29)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1998: Report of the task force (Offsite-box 462, Folder 30-31)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1989-1990: Edit (Offsite-box 462, Folder 32)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1988-1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 462, Folder 33)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1990: First Issue (Offsite-box 462, Folder 34)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 462, Folder 35)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 462, Folder 36)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 462, Folder 37)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 462, Folder 38)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 462, Folder 39)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 462, Folder 40)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 1)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 2)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1995: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 3)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1995: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 4)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1997: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 5)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1997: Publishing [empty] (Offsite-box 463, Folder 6)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1998-: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 7)
  - Entertainment Weekly: 1998: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 8)
  - Family Publication Service (1) (Offsite-box 463, Folder 9)
  - Family Publication Service (2) (Offsite-box 463, Folder 10)
  - Family Publication Service (3) (Offsite-box 463)
  - Family Publication Service (3) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Finance: 1992-: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463)
  - Finance: 1992-: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Food & Wine (Offsite-box 463, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1961: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1961: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1961: Edit: Reports (Offsite-box 463, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1961: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1962: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1962: Edit: Reports (Offsite-box 463, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1962: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1963: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 9/1963: Edit: Stories: Sloan and General Motors (Offsite-box 463)
  - Fortune: 9/1963: Edit: Stories: Sloan and General Motors [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Fortune: 1963: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1963: Edit: Stories: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463)
  - Fortune: 1963: Edit: Stories: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Fortune: 1964: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1964: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1965: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1965: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1965: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1966: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 33)
  - Fortune: 1966: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 34)
  - Fortune: 1966: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 35)
  - Fortune: 1967: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 463, Folder 36)
  - Fortune: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 463, Folder 37)
  - Fortune: 1967: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 38)
  - Fortune: 1967-1974: Edit: Bi-weekly (Offsite-box 463, Folder 39)
  - Fortune: 1968: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 40)
  - Fortune: 1968: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 41)
  - Fortune: 1969: Edit (Offsite-box 463, Folder 42)
  - Fortune: 1969: Publishing (Offsite-box 463, Folder 43)
  - Fortune: 1970: Anniversary, 40th: Background material: Special Environment issue (Offsite-box 463, Folder 44)
  - Fortune: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 464, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 464, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1970: Publishing (Offsite-box 464)
  - Fortune: 1970: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Fortune: 1970: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 464, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1971: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 464, Folder 5-6)
  - Fortune: 1971: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 464, Folder 7-8)
  - Fortune: 1971: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1972: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 464, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1972: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-July (Offsite-box 464)
  - Fortune: 1972: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-July [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Fortune: 1972: Edit: Miscellaneous: August-December (Offsite-box 464, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1972: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1972: New reduced size, 9"x11": First issue (Offsite-box 464, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1973: Edit (Offsite-box 464, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1973: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1974: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 7/1974: Edit: Stories: Federal Reserve Board (Offsite-box 464, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1974: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1975: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1978: Publishing [empty] (Offsite-box 464, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1975: Harrison House Meeting, Glencove, L.I.: Jan. 24-26 (Offsite-box 464, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1976-1978: Bi-weekly (Offsite-box 464, Folder 24-25)
  - Fortune: 1976: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1976: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1977: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1977: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1978: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1979: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 464, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1979: Publishing (Offsite-box 464, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th: Anthology Issue (Offsite-box 465, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th: Anthology Issue: Interviews (Offsite-box 465, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 25th of Fortune 500 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1980: Anniversary, 50th (Offsite-box 465, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 465, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 465, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1983: New format (Offsite-box 465, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1984: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1985: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 465, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1986: Letters Reports [empty] (Offsite-box 465, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1990: Anniversary, 60th: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 465, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1990: 60th Anniversary Issue (Offsite-box 465, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 33)
  - Fortune: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 34)
  - Fortune: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 35)
  - Fortune: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 36)
  - Fortune: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 37)
  - Fortune: 1995: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 38)
  - Fortune: 1995: Publishing (Offsite-box 465, Folder 39)
  - Fortune Book Club (Offsite-box 465, Folder 40)
  - Fortune International: 1983 and Before (Offsite-box 465, Folder 41)
  - Fortune International: 1983: First Issue (Offsite-box 465, Folder 42)
  - Fortune International: 1984 (Offsite-box 465)
  - Fortune International: 1984 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - FSB: 2002: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 44)
  - FYI [employee newsletter] (Offsite-box 463, Folder 13)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 45)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 465, Folder 46)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 465)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1965: Sept.-Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1966 (Offsite-box 465, Folder 48)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 465)
  - General Learning Corporation: 1967-1974 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Golf magazine (Offsite-box 465, Folder 51)
  - Growth Markets Group (Offsite-box 465, Folder 52)
  - Grupo Editorial Expansion (Offsite-box 465, Folder 53)
  - Havers Hills: 1971 & Later (Offsite-box 465, Folder 54)
  - Health: Edit (Offsite-box 465, Folder 55)
  - Home Box Office: Organization flow chart (Offsite-box 465, Folder 56)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Programming (Offsite-box 465)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Programming [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Regulatory (Offsite-box 465, Folder 58)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 465)
  - Home Box Office: 1972 & Before: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Personnel & Organization (Offsite-box 466, Folder 3)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Programming (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Programming [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Regulatory (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Regulatory [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1973: Studio & Network (Offsite-box 466, Folder 6)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Personnel & Organization (Offsite-box 466, Folder 7)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Programming (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Programming [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Regulatory (Offsite-box 466, Folder 9)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Sales & marketing program guide (Offsite-box 466, Folder 10)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Studio & Network (Offsite-box 466, Folder 11)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1974: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Programming (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Programming [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory (Offsite-box 466, Folder 17)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory: Satellite (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Regulatory: Satellite [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Satellite: First Launch (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1975: Satellite: First Launch [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Ventures (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1976: Ventures [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1977: Regulatory (Offsite-box 466, Folder 23)
  - Home Box Office: 1977: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 24)
  - Home Box Office: 1978: Showtime: Viacom-Teleprompter join venture (Offsite-box 466, Folder 25)
  - Home Box Office: 1978: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 26)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Merrill Lynch video seminar (Offsite-box 466, Folder 27)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466)
  - Home Box Office: 1979: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Home Box Office: 1980: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 29)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Programming (Offsite-box 466, Folder 30)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Regulatory: Premiere (Offsite-box 466, Folder 31)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 32)
  - Home Box Office: 1981: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 33)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Tri-Star Pictures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 35)
  - Home Box Office: 1982: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 36)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 37)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 38)
  - Home Box Office: 1983: Programming (Offsite-box 466, Folder 39)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Programming (Offsite-box 466, Folder 40)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 41)
  - Home Box Office: 1984: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 42)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Programming (Offsite-box 466, Folder 43)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 44)
  - Home Box Office: 1985: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 466, Folder 45)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Programming (Offsite-box 466, Folder 46-47)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Ventures (Offsite-box 466, Folder 48)
  - Home Box Office: 1986: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 1-2)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 3)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 4)
  - Home Box Office: 1987: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 5)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 6)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 7)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Video Unit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 8)
  - Home Box Office: 1988: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 9)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 10)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 11)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Video Unit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 12)
  - Home Box Office: 1989: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 13)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Independent productions (Offsite-box 467, Folder 14)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 15)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 16)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Video Unit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 17)
  - Home Box Office: 1990: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 18)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Enterprises (Offsite-box 467, Folder 19)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Independent productions [empty] (Offsite-box 467, Folder 20)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 21)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 22)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 23)
  - Home Box Office: 1991: Video Unit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 24)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Enterprises [empty] (Offsite-box 467, Folder 25)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 26)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 27)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 28)
  - Home Box Office: 1992: Video Unit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 29)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 30)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 31)
  - Home Box Office: 1993: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 32)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 33)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 34)
  - Home Box Office: 1994: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 35)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Programming (Offsite-box 467, Folder 36)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 467, Folder 37)
  - Home Box Office: 1995: Ventures (Offsite-box 467, Folder 38)
  - Information Systems (Offsite-box 467, Folder 39)
  - Inland Container Corporation: 1978 & Later (Offsite-box 467, Folder 40)
  - In Style: 1994-: Edit (Offsite-box 467, Folder 41)
  - In Style: 1994-: Publishing (Offsite-box 467, Folder 42)
  - International: Russia (Offsite-box 467, Folder 43)
  - International (TLI): 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 44)
  - International (TLI): 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 45)
  - International (TLI): 1966-1972 (Offsite-box 467, Folder 46)
  - International (TLI): 1973 & Later (Offsite-box 468, Folder 1)
  - IPC (Offsite-box 468, Folder 2)
  - Legal Department: 1961-1978 (Offsite-box 468)
  - Legal Department: 1961-1978 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Legal Department: 1979- (Offsite-box 468)
  - Legal Department: 1979- [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Letters Magazine (Offsite-box 468)
  - Letters Magazine [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life magazine (Offsite-box 468, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Flavio (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Flavio [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Civil Defense [empty] (Offsite-box 468, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 468, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Fred Schwartz case (1) (Offsite-box 468, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Fred Schwartz case (2) (Offsite-box 468, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Life Society (Offsite-box 468, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 468, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: April-May (Offsite-box 468, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-August (Offsite-box 468, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1961: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 468, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1961: Anniversary, 25th (Offsite-box 468, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1961: Publishing (Offsite-box 468, Folder 21)